mytalkdesk.com 2014-10-16

# Talkdesk

## Talkdesk Privacy Policy

When You register for a Talkdesk account you can be certain that we have implemented comprehensive security practices to ensure that only You and those people You provide authorized access to can see your account information. We respect your right to privacy and feel it is important for You to know how we handle the information we receive from You via our website at www.talkdesk.com (the “Site”) and through our on-demand support platform, tools and services offered on the Site (the “Service”).

### Information You Provide

When You register for the Service, we ask for information such as your name, company name and address and e-mail address. When you register, You are not required to enter your credit card information until You decide to continue with a paid plan. Talkdesk uses a third-party intermediary to manage credit card processing. This intermediary is not permitted to store, retain, or use your billing information except for the sole purpose of credit card processing on Talkdesk’s behalf.

You can modify your account information at anytime by clicking on the Admin link in the global navigation bar at the top of the screen. Talkdesk’s practice is not to use such personal information for marketing purposes. Talkdesk may use the collected personal information and other information Talkdesk collects about your use of the Service to operate and make the Service available to You, for billing, identification and authentication, to contact You about your use of the Service, research purposes and to generally improve the content and functionality of the Service and Site.

Talkdesk may also transmit or share your personal information with its third party vendors and hosting partners to provide the necessary hardware, software, networking, storage, and other technology and services required to operate and maintain the Service, which may require that your personal information be transferred from Your current location to the offices and servers of Talkdesk and the authorized third parties referred to here. Although Talkdesk owns the software, code, databases, all rights to the Talkdesk application, You retain all rights to your data.

### Cookies

When You visit the Site or use the Service, we use session “cookies” – a piece of information stored on your computer – to allow the Site or Service to uniquely identify your browser while You are logged in and to enable Talkdesk to process your online transactions. Session cookies also help us confirm your identity and are required in order to use the Service. Talkdesk uses persistent cookies that only Talkdesk can read and use, to identify You as a Talkdesk customer and make it easier for You to log in to the Service. Users who disable their web browsers’ ability to accept cookies will be able to browse our Site, but will not be able to access or take advantage of the Service.

As You browse Talkdesk, advertising cookies will be placed on your computer so that we can understand what you are interested in. Our display advertising partner, [AdRoll](https://app.adroll.com/), then enables us to present you with retargeting advertising on other sites based on your previous interaction with Talkdesk. The techniques our partners employ do not collect personal information such as your name, email address, postal address or telephone number. You can visit [this page](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/) to opt out of AdRoll and their partners’ targeted advertising.

### Information Sharing

Except as described in this policy, Talkdesk will not give, sell, rent, or loan any identifiable personal information to any third party. We may disclose such information to respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims. We may also share such information if we believe it is necessary in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of our Terms of Service, or as otherwise required by law. Talkdesk may also provide non-personal, summary or group statistics about our customers, sales, traffic patterns, and related Site information to reputable third-party vendors, but these statistics will include no personally identifying information.

### Children’s Personal Information

The Service and Site are not intended for, nor does Talkdesk knowingly collect any personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13.

### Protection of Information

Talkdesk maintains reasonable security measures to protect your information from loss, destruction, misuse, unauthorized access or disclosure. These technologies help ensure that your data is safe, secure, and only available to You and to those You provided authorized access. However, no data transmission over the Internet or information storage technology can be guaranteed to be 100% secure.

### Changes to Privacy Policy

Talkdesk may update this policy from time to time. You can review the most current version of this privacy policy at any time at http://www.talkdesk.com/privacy. Your continued use of the Site or Service constitutes your agreement to be bound by such changes to the privacy policy. Your only remedy, if You do not accept the terms of this privacy policy, is to discontinue use of the Site and Service.

### Business Transactions.

Talkdesk may assign or transfer this privacy policy, and your user account and related information and data, to any person or entity that acquires or is merged with Talkdesk.

### Terms of Service.

When You access and use the Service, You are subject to the Talkdesk Terms of Service.

### Contact Us

If You have questions regarding this privacy policy or about the security practices of Talkdesk, please contact us by email at hello@talkdesk.com.
